Hey, guys!
This is Miss Asuna.
Miss Asuna, this is my
guild, the Sleeping Knights!
My name's June. What's up? How's it going?
Hi, Miss Asuna.
I'm talking.
It's nice to meet you.
You really need to get a
grip on those nerves, Tal.
Seriously.
Every time you meet a girl, you
turn into a blubbering mess.
Anyway, my name's Nori. Glad to meet ya.
My name is Siyune.
It's wonderful to meet you.
And thank you so much for coming today.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name's Techi.
And?
I'm Yuki, the leader of
this guild, kinda sorta.
Miss Asuna, don't laugh.
But see, we want to be the only
guild to beat the boss on this floor.
And we want you to help us! Huh?
Huh?
Thank you.
That's very ambitious, but a boss raid
usually takes at least 49 players.
That's seven parties with
seven players apiece.
So no matter how skilled you are with
just seven players, that's kind of...
Well, to be perfectly
honest, it's unrealistic.
Yeah, it sort of is, isn't it?
We tried taking on the bosses
on Floor 25 and 6 the same way.
Huh?
Just you six?
Yep.
And if you ask me, we put
up a pretty good fight, too.
But both times,
this huge guilt swooped in and beat him
before we could figure out our next move.
Why would you even risk it?
That's a story.
It goes back to when we met
in another GamesNet community.
We hit it off right away, and
we've been friends ever since.
But we only have until next
spring to go on quests together.
Since our time's limited, we
wanted to make the most of it.
You see, come spring, we'll
all be busy with other things.
So we decided that before
we disbanded the guild,
we had to do something so amazing, so
unbelievable, we'd remember it forever.
So that's why you want to
do this boss raid. Exactly.
If we defeat a boss together,
our names will be inscribed
on the Monument of Swordsmen.
You know, the one in the Town of
Beginnings, in the Black Iron Palace.
I know it sounds silly, and
maybe even a little vain,
but we really want to get our names
up on that wall, no matter what.
But getting them on there's the hard part.
If a boss is defeated by a party,
then all of its members will get
their names inscribed on the monument.
But if it's beaten by multiple
parties working in tandem,
only the names of the party
leaders get inscribed.
That's the catch.
If we want the names of everyone in
the sleeping nights up on that wall,
we have to beat the boss.
Together, just us, no one else.
So we talked it over
and came up with a plan.
A party can have up to seven
players max. Therefore,
we decided to find someone as strong or
even stronger than our most powerful player,
Yuki,
and hope whoever we found
accepted our invitation.
I get it.
That's why you were dueling.
Well, what do you think
about joining up with us?
We can't pay you very much, but
you're welcome to what we have.
Oh no, that's okay.
Boss rates cost a fortune as it is,
so you should use your money for that.
I'd feel horrible taking
your money, really.
If you want, you could give me whatever
the boss drops and I'll be fine.
Really?
Then you'll join our party?
This is nothing like
how the old Aincrad was.
And yet, here I am thinking about
safety margins and the odds of winning.
Having safe fights and certain victories.
There's more fun to games than that!
I bet Yuki and her
friends already know this.
Better than I do.
Okay, let's see how far we can go. Yes!
In the end, it's not about winning
or losing, it's having fun.
Thanks a bunch, Miss Asuna!
Please, I'd prefer it if
you just called me Asuna.
Then you can call me Yuki.
That reminds me, Miss Yuki, sorry, Yuki,
the duel was all about
testing players, right?
Yep, pretty much.
Then you must have gone up against a ton
of strong players before I showed up.
Do you remember ever fighting
a spriggan dressed in black?
he would have been using a
one-handed sword huh you know
what I do man he was pretty tough
then why didn't you ask him to
help you out I don't know he
just wasn't right well why not
he found out my secret I can't
have that okay so for tomorrow.
How about we meet back here at 1?
You got it!
And let's have fun. Great!
Mom, what are you doing?
Last month, when you were late for dinner,
I told you it better not happen again.
And here we are.
You're late because of that game,
so now you lose your privileges.
I just lost track of time.
That's my fault, and I'm sorry.
But you didn't have to go and
pull the plug on me like that.
You could have shaken me
or even yelled in my ear.
I would have gotten an alert in-game,
and then I could have logged out and…
I tried that approach before.
It took you five minutes to
snap out of it, remember?
Well, yeah.
I had to say goodbye to
everyone before I logged in.
Oh, don't give me that.
What you do in some stupid
virtual game does not
take priority over your commitments
in the real world. Ever.
I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful next time.
This will be your last warning.
If you break your word to me because of
that thing again, I'm confiscating it.
I have no idea what's going
on in that head of yours.
You lost two years of
your life because of that…
That infernal machine,
you could have died.
How can you even stand to look at it?
This isn't the nerve gear, Mother.
It's dinner time.
Get changed and come downstairs.
I'm not hungry.
As you wish.
I don't know.
ORGAN PLAYS
Sounds like a good lineup, right?
Asuna!
So, Yuki, Jun,
and Tachi are up front, then
Tolkien and Nori are mid-range,
and Siyune are the backup? Right.
Then I guess, if you're covered, maybe
I should hang back as the rear guard.
Yeah, sorry.
I feel bad you're not up front
when you're so good with a sword.
Oh, I don't mind at all.
I'm afraid I'm not much good as a tank.
And anyway,
I'm curious to see whether June and
Tetchy can survive a proper beatdown.
Don't worry about us.
We can handle it.
I guess we'll try.
Oh, this is good.
All right, ready to go take a
peek at that boss room? Yeah!
Yeah!
What a team.
I wonder if they really need me after all.
I can't believe how quickly you
guys are clearing the labyrinth.
You're an amazing group of players.
It's the boss room!
Come on!
Yuki, hold it!
Look!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hang on, hang on!
We're not here to fight you!
Then lower your weapons, now!
Get rid of it!
Keep your eye on them, and if they
make a move for their weapons,
hit them with an Aquabine
spell. You got it.
This is our first ever PvP in Halo.
It's kind of thrilling.
If you're not PKers, then
why were you hiding from us?
We were waiting for someone.
We were hiding because we didn't want to
get hit by a mob before
our friends got here.
You know how it is.
All right, then.
We're here to take on the boss, so
if you're not ready to enter yet?
We'd like to take a crack at it first!
No, that's cool.
We'll just hang here, you
know, till our buddies show up.
Oh and uh, watch your backs in there!
Good luck.
Don't give those dudes a second thought!
Come on, let's do this!
Don't worry, let's Let's just stick to
the plan and have a look inside, okay?
Okay.
Instead of just scoping it out, let's
bust in there and trash the boss.
If you want to try, go for it.
Just make sure not to use any of your
expensive potions and stuff to recover.
Siune and I will support you with
healing spells, so fight hard,
but try not to get too far in the red.
Right on, coach!
Listen up.
If you die, don't respawn right away.
Just hang out and study
the boss's attack patterns.
Then let's meet back at the Lombard save
point and talk about what we learned, okay?
Roger that!
Let's get him! Right!
Jeez!
We got our butts kicked!
What kind of attack was that?
That's gotta be against the rules!
That boss sure knows how to defend itself.
Do you think that's a random move?
Using his arms to block?
And we fought so hard, too!
Hey! What's wrong?
Come here, you guys.
Gather round.
Huh?
I know you're tired, but we need to talk.
Remember those three guys
standing by the boss room?
Sure. Why?
They were scouts from a guild
that specializes in boss raids.
What?
If another guild tries to hit that boss
room, their job is to sit back and watch.
The bosses you tried to raid on the
previous floor and the one before that?
I have a feeling they were there, too.
I had no idea they were even there.
They didn't get in our way or try to
stop us, so they're definitely spies.
All they want is intel.
And when a small guild like the Sleeping
Knights comes along to take on a boss,
We're helping them figure out all
its attack patterns and weaknesses.
Wait a sec.
The door shut behind us when we were inside,
and they definitely didn't follow us.
So, if they can't see
us fighting the boss,
how are they going to
gather any intel on it?
Actually, they could see us fight.
Towards the end there, I looked over and
I saw a tiny gray lizard near June's feet.
That's when I realized I
let my guard down too soon.
It's a dark spell called peeping.
It binds a familiar to a player
and the caster sees what it sees.
So what you're saying is,
after we got hammered by the
bosses on floors 25 and 6,
that other guild swooping in and
beating them, that wasn't a coincidence?
No, I'm afraid it wasn't.
You probably fought so
hard the boss used every
move it had against you
and they saw it all.
That's how they beat
the bosses so quickly.
They used us again.
Now they know everything
about this boss, too.
They're probably in there taking it down.
Those dicks. Damn it. Easy, guys.
Don't count us out just yet.
But what can we do about it now? Simple.
It's 2.30 p .m. in the real world.
At this time of day and
on such short notice,
it'll be hard to find enough
people for a raid party.
By my estimate, it should
take them at least an hour.
That's plenty of time for us.
So here's the deal.
After this, if we can get back to that
room in 30 minutes, we can take it.
Okay?
Yeah!
Last one there's a rotten egg!
Hey, wait for us!
Slow bump!
Crap.
We're too late.
Don't worry.
They won't advance with only 20 players.
We should have enough time to give it
one more try before the rest show up.
You think?
Excuse me.
We'd like to try the boss before you do.
Could you guys let us by?
Sorry, Dollface.
The boss room's off-limits for now.
Wait, off-limits?
What's that supposed to mean?
It means in a couple minutes, the rest
of the guild's gonna roll up here.
We're just holding the room till they do.
If you want, you can wait over there.
And how long do you expect us to wait?
Um, another hour or so?
But we don't have that kind of time.
If you were going in right now,
well, that's a different story.
But you're not, so let us go in first.
Look, I don't make the rules.
I'm just a grunt here, following
orders like everyone else, okay?
Hey, you got a complaint?
Go to the guild headquarters
and talk to them.
It's over in Ygg City,
so get - Are you kidding?
That's far away!
It'd take us at least
an hour to get there!
Hey, big guy. Hmm?
Just trying to figure things out here.
So, no matter how nice we ask,
you're not gonna let us get by you.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, that's it.
That's pretty much what I'm saying.
Okay, if that's what you're saying.
You wanna fight?
But Yuki, are you sure?
Asuna, sometimes you gotta
fight to get your point across.
You know, like how dead serious
you are about something.
Just saying.
Yep, that's pretty much how it is.
You guys...
These folks know exactly
what I'm talking about.
They look like the serious types.
We could chop away all day, and they'd
defend this room to the last player.
Right, pig guy?
We got orders to...
Come on, draw your sword.
You little punk, I'm gonna
make you pay for that.
Sometimes you gotta fight
to get your point across.
Yeah, she's right.
Hey, guys!
I should have dealt with
this when I had the chance.
Sorry, Asuna.
My big mouth got you into this mess.
But it was totally worth it!
Know why?
Because just now, I saw the best
smile I've ever seen on you!
In that case, I'll
start pulling my weight.
We might not take down this boss.
But the next one, I
promise, that one's ours!
Some folks just don't know when to quit.
Sorry, guys.
Stand down.
You're not getting past me.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
I want to see you